<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homework on Xiang WEI</title>
    <link>https://winsa24.github.io/tags/homework/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homework on Xiang WEI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;C. Wang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;R. Ma&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://winsa24.github.io/tags/homework/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Lab 5: VR Locomotion Implementation</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p5/</guid>
      <description>Initial ideas&amp;hellip; I tried to implement this technique on a simple scene in unity and tested it myself. But It doesn’t work well and also bring me a lot fatigue by forcing my arm behind my shoulder. And I also tested with one of my friends and received some feedback from her. During our discussion and we thought to remove the moving back option and also augment the turning. 2nd Round Design&amp;hellip; In this version, player will only use their hand to control [rotation].</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 6: Design Processes and Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/l6/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/l6/</guid>
      <description>Prototyping &amp;amp; Evaluation Human Techniques : Ethnographies, Focus Groups and Interviews&amp;hellip;
Design Prototype Low-Fi Tools Horizontal and Vertical Prototype Evaluate • Lab study • Field study • Survey • Grounded Theory/ Thematic Analysis Some [Guide] or [Restriction] in evaluation  Example&amp;hellip;  [Problem] How to solve fatigue or use small motion to realize big movement? some interesting [Solutions]: Homework Evaluate your Locomotion Technique  Link to a large Locomotion Technique Lib  How to evaluate? Result General result We filled in all our evaluation result in table.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 4: Parkour</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p4/</guid>
      <description>How to open a folder as a Unity Project Double-clicking Scene file opens the project in unity. (It might cause crash of Unity). Then restart hub and select a unity version for it.
My Locomotion Technique ideas&amp;hellip; Inspiration
  Rocketer (Click to check the presentation slide) On class example for presenting the idea: Target : Develop a Swimming Technique in VR Requirements: Make user feel that they are moving forward or backward Method: detect distance and have the matrix Evaluate: Set a Goal: perform best swimming experience</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 3: VR Unity Selection</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p3/</guid>
      <description>New knowledge:  Last post mistake: There are difference between tags and layers:
Tags are used for finding objects with a specific tag ( e.g. FindWithTag(str) ). Layers can be used to identify objects at a high level
  There are also other interesting tutorials to follow&amp;hellip; https://www.youtube.com/c/DilmerValecillos/videos
https://sidequestvr.com/app/578/handspace
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A0gpaQGu_H0
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPFU30tbyKs
 Deploy my Roll-A-Ball on Oculus  try to use the build and run directly from Unity but fail.   try to review all the undo step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 2: Roll-A-Ball</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p2/</guid>
      <description>Get start with Unity&amp;hellip; Some New knowledge in Unity for me:  Customize Script Editor:   Unity Lifecycle: Start ( ) / FixedUpdate( ) / Update( )  Start to implement a Simple Roll-A-Ball Game following Wenjie&amp;rsquo;s Slides!  Skipped step: transform Empty GameObject In my scene, I don&amp;rsquo;t need to change the transform matrix of the Wall in general.
  Import TMP: Unshown steps in the tutorial
It works with only importing the essential package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 1: Setup Blog &amp; Unity</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/p1/</guid>
      <description>Setup your own Blog Like this&amp;hellip; Generally follow this link
 Install Hugo on macOS (Homebrew):  Type in console:
- brew install hugo   Register on Git Create Page  - hugo new site sitename - cd sitename   Select Theme  - git init - cd themes - git submodule add https://github.com/budparr/gohugotheme-ananke.git themes/ananke  Open config.toml in a text editor and add theme = &amp;ldquo;ananke&amp;rdquo;
Local test - hugo server -D  See http://localhost:1313/ in the browser.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture I: Introduction and History of Virtual Reality</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/l1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/courses/igd301/l1/</guid>
      <description>Idea you can gain from the class&amp;hellip; HCI: Moore’s Law : Ex. Microwave
No intuitive design, but have good design : intelligently leverages cognitive and perceptual abilities
Ex. Tap Definition: History: VR : rise and fall and rise Homework Section 1 Two scenario describe that MR could cause problems for users. Based on VIDEO Hyper - Reality : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YJg02ivYzSs
Scenario 1:
The adopted pet in the supermarket might bit the user if he doesn’t get what he want.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
