<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BJUT on Xiang WEI</title>
    <link>https://winsa24.github.io/tags/bjut/</link>
    <description>Recent content in BJUT on Xiang WEI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;C. Wang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;R. Ma&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 02:01:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://winsa24.github.io/tags/bjut/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualization Recommendation System</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/web1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/web1/</guid>
      <description>Visualization Recommendation System This subject designs and implements a set of visualization scheme recommendation system. The system is oriented to data analysts whose requirements are not clear and who do not have professional programming capabilities. Through simple interactions, the system generates a series of visualization solutions that meet users’ needs. The design of the system is based on the actual analysis of visual element properties, attributes and real cases. By separating its data, properties and attributes, the corresponding relationship among them is studied and defined, and the model is established accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Design of Software Engineering</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/software/</guid>
      <description>SmartHome WeChat Mini Program A software that can remotely, link and manage smart devices at home, and has security alarm and device self-checking functions. To meet the remote control of the equipment, it can control the equipment to realize the corresponding function or make the corresponding response to change the indoor lighting, temperature and other environmental conditions before returning home. It can realize the security alarm function, detect the parameters of the sensor equipment, realize the timely alarm of abnormal conditions, and ensure the health of family members and the safety of property.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Design of Computer Hardware</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/hardware/</guid>
      <description>SmartHome App A small tool for real-time monitoring of indoor air quality is designed, which can display the current indoor temperature and humidity, formaldehyde concentration and smoke. And realize the analysis of air quality over a period of time on the mobile phone and provide suggestions for improvement.
Function description Smoke sensor and formaldehyde sensor obtain their respective data and pass it to the development board; The mobile phone can be connected to the development board via software using Bluetooth, and receive real-time data from the board; The software can process the air quality data, draw a line graph, and provide it to users for analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Design of Data Structure</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/qt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/qt1/</guid>
      <description>Wrote “2018 World Cup inquiring system” by VS and QT independently, studied knowledge of front-end and back-end development, realized the function of inquiring information of games in a specific date selected by dragging roller and showing all kinds of real-time statistical results.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>