<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IP Paris on Xiang WEI</title>
    <link>https://winsa24.github.io/tags/ip-paris/</link>
    <description>Recent content in IP Paris on Xiang WEI</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;C. Wang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;R. Ma&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://winsa24.github.io/tags/ip-paris/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ReversedVRMove</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/reversedvrmove/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/reversedvrmove/</guid>
      <description>Reversed VR Move What will happpen if you are moving in a reversed world ?
Want to go left but actually go right ? Going backward to move forward !
Some experience you will NEVER gain in our real physical world ! How will you adapt to it ? How will it impact on us ?
Download from github Play instruction Please check inside the game ^ ^
Video 
Motivation The goal of this project is to explore the impact of VR on people&amp;rsquo;s activities in the physical world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food Atlas - Local Food Around the World</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/foodatlas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/foodatlas/</guid>
      <description>We have made a food atlas based on augmented reality technology. This map can help people, especially children, understand and memorize the typical food of various places through having fun with the matching games. The user needs to recognize the map with the camera of the smartphone, and select the country they want to explore by clicking on the map. After starting the game, there are going to show five models of local specialties. The user needs to select the corresponding word card according to the model.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ARcher</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/archer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/archer/</guid>
      <description>ARcher The purpose of our application is to create an AR game that anyone can use in their home. In our case we use as basis the basic deck of card that almost everyone has. In our demo, we include 4 different kind of cards : 1) Ace of Spades 2) Two of Spades 3) Eight of Spades 4) Five of Hearts. The beautiful of this implementation is that one is able to create non-linear platform levels with the same cards andthis is the main motivation behind our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DriveKour (VR Locomotion Develop)</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/drivekour/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/drivekour/</guid>
      <description>Drivekour Game Based on the Parkour Game developed by Wenjie, we implement our locomotion technique and also add some IP Paris feature. Download from github Play instruction Video</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xperience of Virtual Plants (XVP)</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/xvp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/xvp/</guid>
      <description>Xperience of Virtual Plants (XVP) An application to help users learn rare plants. The system will generate 3D models based on different image targets. By clicking on the virtual buttons and screen buttons, users can interact with 3D models.
Target Device An Android equipment with API Level above 19 (4.4 ‘KitKat’)
Development Platform MacOs Mojave (10.14.6) + Unity (2019.2.13f1) + Vuforia (9.4.6)
Final video Check the video to better learn our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Develop Practice</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/web2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/web2/</guid>
      <description> Created a currency converter which allows users can get the product of two entered number. Created a searching engine which allows users to filter the list with student name or module name. Created a space shooting game based on the animations and functions.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currency-Converter</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/android2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/android2/</guid>
      <description>Created a currency-converter based on Android Studio. The users can enter different amount and select types of convert. The app will automatically read the rate from a given URL, and update the result on the interface immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing Tool</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/qt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/projects/qt2/</guid>
      <description>Created a simple drawing application based on Qt toolkit (which I’ve tried to use in the Course Design of Data Structures in my undergraduate study). The application has an interactive interface which allows users to draw multiple shapes in different colors, line styles and thickness, by clicking buttons or dragging sliders. Users can also select an existing shape and move, resize or change attributes of it. It also allows users to read or save the images.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
