<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors on Eureka Demo</title>
    <link>https://winsa24.github.io/authors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Authors on Eureka Demo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;C. Wang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;R. Ma&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 22:52:56 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://winsa24.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Xiang WEI</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/authors/example-author/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 22:52:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/authors/example-author/</guid>
      <description>Xiang WEI contact: email: xiang.wei@ip-paris.fr
EDUCATION  On going: MSc Computer Science (Interaction, Graphic and Design) at Institut Polytechnique de Paris (IP Paris). (Expected 2020-2022) Exchange at EFREI Paris (2020) BSc Computer Science from Beijing University of Technology (BJUT). (2016-2020)  EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES  Vice minister of the Department of Social Practice in the Communist Youth League in Beijing University of Technology. Organized and managed volunteer activities, recruitment and other activities; communicated and collaborated with different departments; applied for activity funds and held social practice results report meeting Assistant English teacher volunteer at Association Carcajada De Villena, Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Authors</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/authors/hugo-authors/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/authors/hugo-authors/</guid>
      <description>Vestibulum vel arcu Donec interdum justo sed posuere imperdiet. Quisque nec mauris eu erat mattis egestas in vitae nisl. Sed nisl augue, congue sed quam quis, tempor tempus nibh. Pellentesque accumsan in quam a interdum. Morbi iaculis venenatis lacinia. Mauris quis nisl vitae nisi mollis placerat id vel ligula. Integer vitae arcu ac leo iaculis rhoncus id vitae dolor. Fusce quis nisl tincidunt, vulputate dolor quis, mollis massa. Donec congue velit at risus cursus, eu auctor dolor rhoncus.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
