<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wei Xiang on Hugo</title>
    <link>https://winsa24.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Wei Xiang on Hugo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>[Home](/) &amp;#183; Theme [Simpleness](https://github.com/winsa24/simpleness) Powered by [Hugo](https://gohugo.io/)</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://winsa24.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Explore</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/vrexplore/1218/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/vrexplore/1218/</guid>
      <description>Nicely video drive me back to the past Even drive me to some impossible angle or unseen area   Figure out how to screenshot and export them ^^ export:
  Go to SideQuest Click the File icon on the top tool bar Clike the Oculus icon below Then you will see the screenshots you took and click save icon, find a place on your computer:)     Notes: Ways to update the pages:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 4: Parkour</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p4/</guid>
      <description>How to open a folder as a Unity Project Double-clicking Scene file opens the project in unity. (It might cause crash of Unity). Then restart hub and select a unity version for it.
 12.22 Try to apply joystick but all operation are mirrorred. =========
  Notes:
Ways to update the pages:
Git command as follow:
rm -rf docs (optional)
Hugo
git add .
git commit -m “something&amp;quot;
git push origin master</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 4: VR Technology and Perception</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l4/</guid>
      <description> Sensation developed other than hand   two types of haptic Ungrounded vs Grounded ad: flexiblity easier to control dis: limited force on human can&amp;rsquo;t adapat to all situation  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 3: VR Unity Selection</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p3/</guid>
      <description>New knowledge:  Last post mistake: There are difference between tags and layers:
Tags are used for finding objects with a specific tag ( e.g. FindWithTag(str) ). Layers can be used to identify objects at a high level
  push depth&amp;hellip;.
  other interaction ways&amp;hellip;.
  links post in chat:
https://twitter.com/pushmatrix/status/1333773295385194502
https://www.youtube.com/c/DilmerValecillos/videos
https://sidequestvr.com/app/578/handspace
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=A0gpaQGu_H0
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPFU30tbyKs
 Test on Oculus  try to use the build and run directly from Unity but fail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 3: VR Technology and Perception</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l3/</guid>
      <description> Depth percetion Didn&amp;rsquo;t see the shark   On class brainstorm   Gestalt rules https://www.interaction-design.org/literature/topics/gestalt-principles#:~:text=Gestalt%20principles%20or%20laws%20are,the%20separate%20simpler%20elements%20involved.
  Foveated rendering   ? How to link this to the failure of google glass?   Interesting Ideas  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 2: Roll-A-Ball</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p2/</guid>
      <description>New knowledge:  Change to Script Editor:   Unity Lifecycle: Start ( ) / FixedUpdate( ) / Update( )   Skipped step: transform Empty GO   Import TMP: Unshown steps in the tutorial
  Steps order *
   Tried to start game, but can&amp;rsquo;t control the the player. Have no reaction when kicking the keyboard. Find an error when create the Input Actions in the Assest folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lab 1: Setup Blog</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/practices/p1/</guid>
      <description>Successfully set my first Hugo blog, by following https://gohugo.io/hosting-and-deployment/hosting-on-github/
 One thing need to be careful: DON&amp;rsquo;T forget to modify the settings in GitHub settings   Also remind to read the theme&amp;rsquo;s readme If I want to modify the theme, go to https://themes.gohugo.io/
 Link to my blog https://winsa24.github.io/
Need to learn Markdown grammar   Notes: Ways to update the pages:
Git command as follow:
rm -rf docs (optional)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture 2: VR Technology and Perception</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l2/</guid>
      <description>On-class notes: Presence ? Immersive?
VR fly simulation -(extended)&amp;ndash;&amp;gt; VR history tour ? Ex. Based on 清明上河图?
Vergence conflict??
Waiting for the course slide&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lecture I: Introduction and History of Virtual Reality</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/lectures/l1/</guid>
      <description>HCI: Moore’s Law : Ex. Microwave
No intuitive design, but have good design : intelligently leverages cognitive and perceptual abilities
Ex. Tap Definition: History: VR : rise and fall and rise Homework 1 Two scenario describe that MR could cause problems for users. Based on VIDEO Hyper - Reality : https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YJg02ivYzSs
Scenario 1:
The adopted pet in the supermarket might bit the user if he doesn’t get what he want. And the user may have hurt feeling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xperience of Virtual Plants (XVP)</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Nov 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/ar/</guid>
      <description>Based on Unity + Vuforia, created a AR plants guide book to help users learn rare plants. The users can scan a target image and he will see a 3D models. He could also interact with the model by clicking either the virtual buttons or screen buttons. Check the video to better learn our project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Develop Practice</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/web2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/web2/</guid>
      <description> Created a currency converter which allows users can get the product of two entered number. Created a searching engine which allows users to filter the list with student name or module name. Created a space shooting game based on the animations and functions.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Currency-Converter</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/android2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Oct 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/android2/</guid>
      <description>Created a currency-converter based on Android Studio. The users can enter different amount and select types of convert. The app will automatically read the rate from a given URL, and update the result on the interface immediately.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drawing Tool</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/qt2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Sep 2020 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/qt2/</guid>
      <description>Created a simple drawing application based on Qt toolkit (which I’ve tried to use in the Course Design of Data Structures in my undergraduate study). The application has an interactive interface which allows users to draw multiple shapes in different colors, line styles and thickness, by clicking buttons or dragging sliders. Users can also select an existing shape and move, resize or change attributes of it. It also allows users to read or save the images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intelligent Visualization Generator</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/web1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/web1/</guid>
      <description>Independently develop and build a visualization program to generate a website. Through simple and efficient interaction with users, the website generates a series of visualization solutions based on user data to help users perform data analysis;
The website is built based on HTML+CSS+JAVASCRIPT+MYSQL, and the displayed visualization scheme is based on ECHARTS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Design of Software Engineering</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/software/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2019 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/software/</guid>
      <description>Studied the development of WeChat applet, built “Smart Home” applet in group, in charged of front-end logic writing and front and aft link, maintained version update and administrated intra-group cooperation by Git</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Design of Computer Hardware</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/hardware/</guid>
      <description>Engaged in the project of ‘Intelligent home system’, learnt Android development and knowledge about IP, been responsible for the encapsulation of IP and whole construction of the showing App</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Design of Data Structure</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/qt1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Oct 2018 02:01:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/qt1/</guid>
      <description>Wrote “2018 World Cup inquiring system” by VS and QT independently, studied knowledge of front-end and back-end development, realized the function of inquiring information of games in a specific date selected by dragging roller and showing all kinds of real-time statistical results</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2017 12:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/posts/markdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://winsa24.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://winsa24.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Xiang WEI contact: email: xiang.wei@ip-paris.fr
EDUCATION  On going: MSc Computer Science (Interaction, Graphic and Design) at Institut Polytechnique de Paris (IP Paris). (Expected 2020-2022) Exchange at EFREI Paris (2020) BSc Computer Science from Beijing University of Technology (BJUT). (2016-2020)
 EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES  Vice minister of the Department of Social Practice in the Communist Youth League in Beijing University of Technology. Organized and managed volunteer activities, recruitment and other activities; communicated and collaborated with different departments; applied for activity funds and held social practice results report meeting Assistant English teacher volunteer at Association Carcajada De Villena, Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
